[
    {"app_name":"Memorizing Heroes"
    },

    { "category":"GRE",
      "content":[

		{
          "front":"Bilk(1)",
          "back":"cheat",
          "weight":"1"
        },

		{
          "front":"Noxious(2)",
          "back":"harmful",
          "weight":"2"
        },

		{
          "front":"Knotty(3)",
          "back":"complex",
          "weight":"3"
        },

		{
          "front":"Covert(4)",
          "back":"transform",
          "weight":"4"
        },

		{
          "front":"Abrogate(5)",
          "back":"cancel",
          "weight":"5"
        }
      ]
    },

    { "category":"Toelf!",
          "content":[
            {
              "front":"prohibited",
              "back":"fobidden",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"purchase",
              "back":"buy",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"abet",
              "back":"encourage",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"abridge",
              "back":"shorten",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"pursue",
              "back":"chase",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"require",
              "back":"need",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"respond",
              "back":"reply",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"retain",
              "back":"remember",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"select",
              "back":"choose",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"deplore",
              "back":"empty",
              "weight":"0"
            }
          ]
     },

    { "category":"IElTS",
          "content":[
            {
              "front":"symbolise",
              "back":"represent",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"crucial",
              "back":"important",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"task",
              "back":"job",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"obvious",
              "back":"clear",
              "weight":"0"
            },

            {
              "front":"occur",
              "back":"happen",
              "weight":"0"
            }
          ]
    }
]

